

Priyanka Parmar

priyankajanssen@gmail.com | in priyankaparmar

Experienced IT Professional with over 13 years of experience in leading, designing and delivering complex projects and transition programs. Because of my broad experience across many aspects I have led large scale transformation programmes and offshoring projects involving multiple disciplines and partners. My engineering background enables me to quickly grasp new concepts, tools and technologies.

Personal values I hold very dear are honesty, integrity and trust. I believe in it's important to say what you really think and provide an open communication environment therefore I am able to build strong teams and meaningful relationships.

On a side note, I'm absurdly good at eating spicy food. Unfortunately, there's not much of a market for that skill...

Skill Summary

- Machine learning
- Natural language processing
- Robotic Process Automation
- Strategic Planning
- revenue modeling & forecasting
 object oriented programming
- account management
- project planning
- project management
- programme management

- transition management
- complex transformations
- agile
 - o scrum

 - lean
- value chain analysis
 - o ITIL
 - programming

Education

2018 **Nyenrode Business University**

MBA in business and IT, Thesis in Artificial Intelligence in Psychology

2006 **Engineering Univeristy of Mumbai Information Technology**

Bachelor's degree with distinction in engineering

2003 **University of Mumbai**

Diploma in computer science

Languages

- English (Fluent)
- Dutch (level A2 can understand fully, can converse but not business fluent)
- Hindi (Native)

Recent experience

IPSOFT

2017 - Engagement Manager - Cognitive Solutions (Amelia Virtual Agent)

Manage and build positive relationship provide excellent experience to all customers under the Benelux and Nordics region after they signed a contract for implementation of conversational Al agent Amelia.

- Managing client expectations, and working with the sales team to identify additionalopportunities / use cases to implement Amelia to maximize value for the client.
- Build and manage loosely coupled multi- disciplinary delivery of AI engineersTechnical leads and engineers to define solution options, provide estimates on efforand risk, and evaluate technical feasibility.
- Creating technical solution designs, process workflows and running product demos
- Running the client configuration and Integration streams on site and liaise
 with the theorem dedicated IPsoft teams (i.e. Configuration & Implementation
 and Interface Security teams), with the support of the Business and
 Technical Architects to addresmore complex issues
- Helping solve any problems/ issues encountered during implementation with speed anefficiency.

Key Accomplishments:

- Designed technical solution for knowledge base search within the custome environment via text based chat for Amelia Al conversational agent
- Featured in the #WomenInAl initiative to support advancement of women in STEM.

Atos

2016 - 2017 Automation Program Lead

- Ensured effective and efficient management of all aspects of Automation implementation, and improve outcomes for Atos for Robotic Process Automation (RPA) initiative
- Developing reporting strategies and tools for measuring automation rate and success globally (all accounts)
- Reporting the customer Automation status and service operations.
- Monitor implementation of projects and the completion of major milestones to ensure success.

Atos

2015 - 2016 Global tower head networks, data center & communication services

- Responsible and accountable to provide leadership, overall direction, supervision, and planning for the Network Infrastructure & Operations department and its related functions, services, and operations worldwide for Customer Siemens at Atos.
- To ensure the effective and efficient management of all aspects of service delivery, and improve outcomes for Siemens Overall responsibilities include:
- Managing Operational budget, creating financial plans, investment decisions
 Operating and Capital budget responsibility for all network services, as well as prioritization and recommendations of capital investments.

- Ensure quality of practice meets contractual requirements, legal obligations and organizational policy and procedures
- Identify and elevate issues impacting on achievement of service delivery objectives and to continually improve services.
- Provide directions to the Global Network Services Team (offshore and onshore) to ensure the managed service partners have the necessary process, tools, and support to be successful.
- Report to the VP &COO of Siemens account within Atos and ensuring that the long-term strategy is translated into appropriate goals and targets for the team.

Experience

Atos

2015 Global Voice Transformation Manager

- Setting up central operations delivery center in Romania and ensuring service delivery according to contractual obligations as well as managing transformation
- Managing virtual teams based in Romania, Netherlands and Germany.
- Reporting to the customer Transformation Programme status and service operations.
- Managing customer relationships, conducting weekly reviews, setting up the service operational structure.
- Driving end to end transformation and coordinating and managing different stakeholders in the chain.
- Responsible for creating business development plan, working with the account and sales team to develop new solutions and resource units to add to the service Catalogue.

Atos

2013 - 2014 Global Transformation and offshore manager

- Responsible for development and realization of offshore opportunities within the Net- work services Unit.
- Drove and managed offshore of LAN services from Germany to Poland for the largest customer account of Atos.
- Established a centralized network operations center in Poland for all countries within EMEA region.
- Set up the complete network team organization structure, with clear roles and responsibilities.
- Developed Programme schedule, offshore execution Plan, tracked budget and delivered savings over 5M in one year.
- Scheduled programme activities, reporting directly to the Global tower head of Network operations with programme status and significant issues.
- Lead and manage multiple virtual teams in different countries and cultures (Poland, India, China, and Germany)
- Instrumental in obtaining Legal approval from customer in Germany to ensure compliance of data security requirements.
- Delivered savings of 5M euros in one year by reducing costs of subcontractors and set- ting up offshore delivery center in Poland

2011 - 2013 Transition Programme Manager

- Accountable for replacement of end of life hardware in datacenters with new hardware, for 6000 servers within 12 months in Germany.
 Development, communication, implementation and management of program within the network and other units' servers which run business critical applications for the customer
- Liaise with the business sponsor/lead and project team, lead the development, communication, implementation and management of programme.
- Define the project scope, requirements, outlining costs, resources, timeframes and other related project tasks.
- Have overall responsibility and accountability for end-to-end project management and implementation on all sub projects.
- Monitor implementation of projects and the completion of major milestones to ensure success.
- Report project status and significant issues to the Global Programme lead

Atos

2009 - 2011 Global Lean Sustainability Manager- Benelux, Germany & IMEA

- Responsible for ensuring lean operations of transformed sites within Benelux, Germany and IMEA.
- Oversee ongoing Lean implementation and performance for all IT Managed Services operations within Benelux, Germany and IMEA regions. Audit transformed sites within Benelux, Germany and IMEA region to ensure that they are lean compliant reporting to the Chief Lean officer.
- Build and train audit & support capability. Deliver short and long assessments (audit rollout), in alignment with compliance audit. - Liaise with local Management for Lean follow up and escalation (monthly review).

Continuous improvement:

• Draft plans for operational excellence collaborating together with various operational teams and track implementation.

Atos

2008 Venue Manager

Provide Level 2 real time support for Handball and Gymnastics Venue for the Beijing Olympics 2008. Part of IT team which monitored IT security events to detect potential security risks. Ensured data consistency with Information Diffusion systems and INFO 2008.

Atos

2006 - 2009 ERP consultant (Oracle E Business Suite

Executed the full project life cycle (specializing in HR and payroll modules): requirements gathering, design, technical specifications, generating test scripts, documentation. Con- ducted defect prevention meetings, Causal Analysis and Resolution meetings, product and process quality control and proactive risk management activities.

 Created Technical designs and developments for Oracle Applications modules which included interfaces, customizations, self-service, workflow,

- reports and data migration.
- Delivered full life cycle documentation based on functional design, working closely with the functional team and business to provide quality solutions.
- Maintained comprehensive scheduling & timecard solution integrated into the e-Business Suite which was a mix of OA Framework pages, Workflow and PLSQL used by 5000 employees across 800 stores in the UK.
- Migrated code across all Pre Production environments, liaising with QA and onshore UAT teams as well as provided 3rd line support for all technical components of Oracle Applications.
- Conducted Quality reviews of designs and code developed by other members